

OBJECTIVE

As a game developer, I understand how mechanics can make or break the gameplay experience. As a designer and web developer, I know what a clean, responsive interface can do for your business. I enjoy technical aspects of design & development and polishing critical details that others may overlook. I am fully confident in proving what I say I can do. Contact me and let's work together.

EDUCATION

University of Richmond | Richmond, Virginia | 2019

Currently Enrolled in the Coding Bootcamp managed by Trilogy Education Graduating on October 26th, 2019

- Studying full-stack web development
- Studying API integration and databasing
- Studying command line interface and Git version-control on GitHub

Longwood University | Farmville, Virginia | 2014 -2018

Majored in Graphic Design & Animation with a Bachelors of Fine Arts Graduated on May 19th, 2018

- Studied design elements, principles, visual problem solving, branding & production
- Studied 3D modeling, rigging, animation, texturing & rendering
- Created a fully-playable game in Unity called "TILT" for my senior project
- Member of LAS (Lancer Animation Studios) & the 3D Modeling Club

WORK EXPERIENCE

Target | Midlothian, Virginia | Oct 2018 - Jan 2019

Flexible Fulfillment

- Shopped for online orders and in-store pickups for arriving customers
- Packed and prepared orders for UPS transit

Kroger | Midlothian, Virginia | May 2016 - Feb 2017

Full-Stack Web Development (MERN Stack) API & Database Integration (AJAX/MongoDB/SQL) Command Line Interface, Git Version-Control & Deployment Vector Creation, Image Manipulation & Motion Graphics 3D Modeling, Rigging, Animation, Texturing & Rendering Leadership, Teamwork & Logical Problem Solving

Clicklist Attendant Adobe CC • Shopped for online orders and prepared groceries for arriving customers Blender/Maya • Finalized customer payments car-side & loaded their groceries for them SKILLS & CAPABILITIES Game Development Pipeline (Unity/C#)



^{*}Please visit my portfolio site at <u>ericpowell3d.com</u> for more detailed information